// import shuffleArray from "../helpers/shuffleArray.js";
// import { getRandomItem } from "../helpers/shuffleAnswer.js";

export const TheGooniesQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the pirate whose treasure the Goonies are searching for?",
    options: [
      "One-Eyed Willie",
      "Blackbeard",
      "Captain Hook",
      "Long John Silver",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "One-Eyed Willie",
  },
  {
    question: "What year was 'The Goonies' released?",
    options: ["1985", "1984", "1986", "1987"],
    correctAnswer: "1985",
  },
  {
    question: "Who directed 'The Goonies'?",
    options: [
      "Richard Donner",
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Chris Columbus",
      "Joe Dante",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Richard Donner",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the family trying to foreclose on the Goonies' homes?",
    options: [
      "The Fratellis",
      "The Perkins",
      "The Astoria Country Club",
      "The Walshes",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Astoria Country Club",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Mouth's real name in the movie?",
    options: [
      "Clark Devereaux",
      "Mikey Walsh",
      "Richard Wang",
      "Lawrence Cohen",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Clark Devereaux",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Data's first name?",
    options: ["Richard", "David", "Michael", "Jonathan"],
    correctAnswer: "Richard",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the deformed character befriended by Chunk?",
    options: ["Sloth", "Chunk", "Mouth", "Data"],
    correctAnswer: "Sloth",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the restaurant where Mouth's father works?",
    options: [
      "Lighthouse Lounge",
      "Crab Shack",
      "Ye Olde Fisherman",
      "The Inferno",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Lighthouse Lounge",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the country club that wants to buy out the Goon Docks?",
    options: [
      "Astoria Country Club",
      "Goon Docks Golf Club",
      "Perkins Country Club",
      "Oregon Coast Club",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Astoria Country Club",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the cave where the Goonies find One-Eyed Willie's ship?",
    options: ["Skull Rock", "Inferno", "Treasure Cove", "Pirate's Grotto"],
    correctAnswer: "Inferno",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the town where the Goonies live?",
    options: ["Astoria", "Cannon Beach", "Seaside", "Newport"],
    correctAnswer: "Astoria",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the ship that One-Eyed Willie captained?",
    options: [
      "Inferno",
      "Black Pearl",
      "Flying Dutchman",
      "Queen Anne's Revenge",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Inferno",
  },
  {
    question: "What instrument does Mouth play to open the cave entrance?",
    options: ["Piano", "Organ", "Harmonica", "Accordion"],
    correctAnswer: "Organ",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the eldest Fratelli brother?",
    options: ["Francis", "Jake", "Mama", "Sloth"],
    correctAnswer: "Francis",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the secret password to enter the Goonies' hideout?",
    options: [
      "Goonies never say die",
      "Open sesame",
      "X marks the spot",
      "Ahoy matey",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Goonies never say die",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Mikey and Brand's dog?",
    options: ["Rosalita", "Chunk", "Jake", "Scooby"],
    correctAnswer: "Rosalita",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the convenience store where Chunk performs the Truffle Shuffle?",
    options: [
      "Astoria Mart",
      "7-Eleven",
      "Goon Docks Grocery",
      "Mikey's Mini Mart",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Astoria Mart",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the waterslide that the Goonies use to escape the Fratellis?",
    options: ["Wishing Well", "Pirate's Plunge", "Bone Organ", "Sloth's Slide"],
    correctAnswer: "Wishing Well",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actor who plays Mikey?",
    options: ["Sean Astin", "Corey Feldman", "Josh Brolin", "Jeff Cohen"],
    correctAnswer: "Sean Astin",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actor who plays Mouth?",
    options: ["Corey Feldman", "Sean Astin", "Josh Brolin", "Jeff Cohen"],
    correctAnswer: "Corey Feldman",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actor who plays Brand?",
    options: ["Josh Brolin", "Sean Astin", "Corey Feldman", "Jeff Cohen"],
    correctAnswer: "Josh Brolin",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actor who plays Chunk?",
    options: ["Jeff Cohen", "Sean Astin", "Corey Feldman", "Josh Brolin"],
    correctAnswer: "Jeff Cohen",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actor who plays Data?",
    options: [
      "Ke Huy Quan",
      "Jonathan Ke Quan",
      "Richard Wang",
      "Jonathan Ke Huy Quan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ke Huy Quan",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actor who plays Sloth?",
    options: [
      "John Matuszak",
      "Dolph Lundgren",
      "Andre the Giant",
      "Lou Ferrigno",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "John Matuszak",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actress who plays Mama Fratelli?",
    options: ["Anne Ramsey", "Kathy Bates", "Estelle Harris", "Betty White"],
    correctAnswer: "Anne Ramsey",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actress who plays Andy?",
    options: [
      "Kerri Green",
      "Martha Plimpton",
      "Lori Loughlin",
      "Molly Ringwald",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kerri Green",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the actress who plays Stef?",
    options: [
      "Martha Plimpton",
      "Kerri Green",
      "Lori Loughlin",
      "Molly Ringwald",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Martha Plimpton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the character who says 'Goonies never say die!'?",
    options: ["Mikey", "Mouth", "Data", "Brand"],
    correctAnswer: "Mikey",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the candy bar that Sloth loves?",
    options: ["Baby Ruth", "Snickers", "Hershey's", "3 Musketeers"],
    correctAnswer: "Baby Ruth",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the newspaper company where Mikey and Brand's father works?",
    options: [
      "Astoria Gazette",
      "Goon Docks Times",
      "Oregon Daily",
      "Coastal Chronicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Astoria Gazette",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the invention Data uses to zip-line down to the Inferno?",
    options: [
      "Slick Shoes",
      "Pinchers of Peril",
      "Bully Blinders",
      "Data's Rocket Shoes",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Slick Shoes",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the beach where the Goonies emerge at the end of the movie?",
    options: [
      "Cannon Beach",
      "Ecola State Park",
      "Haystack Rock Beach",
      "Astoria Beach",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cannon Beach",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the state where the movie is set?",
    options: ["Oregon", "Washington", "California", "Maine"],
    correctAnswer: "Oregon",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the restaurant where the Fratellis hide out?",
    options: [
      "Lighthouse Lounge",
      "Fratelli's Italian",
      "Seaside Diner",
      "Pirate's Cove",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Lighthouse Lounge",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the map that leads the Goonies to One-Eyed Willie's treasure?",
    options: ["Copper Bones", "Pirate's Map", "Treasure Map", "Willie's Chart"],
    correctAnswer: "Copper Bones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the device Data uses to punch Francis Fratelli?",
    options: [
      "Pinchers of Peril",
      "Slick Shoes",
      "Bully Blinders",
      "Data's Fist",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Pinchers of Peril",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the song that plays during the opening credits?",
    options: [
      "The Goonies 'R' Good Enough",
      "Goonies Never Say Die",
      "One-Eyed Willie's Gold",
      "Astoria or Bust",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Goonies 'R' Good Enough",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the character who performs the 'Truffle Shuffle'?",
    options: ["Chunk", "Mouth", "Data", "Mikey"],
    correctAnswer: "Chunk",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the youngest Fratelli brother?",
    options: ["Jake", "Francis", "Mama", "Sloth"],
    correctAnswer: "Jake",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the device Data uses to light up the cave?",
    options: [
      "Bully Blinders",
      "Slick Shoes",
      "Pinchers of Peril",
      "Data's Flashlight",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Bully Blinders",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the character who says 'Hey, you guys!'?",
    options: ["Sloth", "Chunk", "Mikey", "Data"],
    correctAnswer: "Sloth",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the pirate ship that the Goonies find?",
    options: [
      "Inferno",
      "Black Pearl",
      "Flying Dutchman",
      "Queen Anne's Revenge",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Inferno",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the character who translates the Spanish instructions for the Goonies?",
    options: ["Mouth", "Data", "Mikey", "Brand"],
    correctAnswer: "Mouth",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the character who is afraid of the dark?",
    options: ["Chunk", "Data", "Mouth", "Andy"],
    correctAnswer: "Chunk",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the character who wears braces?",
    options: ["Mikey", "Data", "Mouth", "Brand"],
    correctAnswer: "Mikey",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the character who is an aspiring inventor?",
    options: ["Data", "Mikey", "Mouth", "Chunk"],
    correctAnswer: "Data",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the character who is the oldest of the Goonies?",
    options: ["Brand", "Mikey", "Mouth", "Data"],
    correctAnswer: "Brand",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the character who is forced to play the organ?",
    options: ["Andy", "Stef", "Mikey", "Data"],
    correctAnswer: "Andy",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the character who is allergic to bullets?",
    options: ["Data", "Chunk", "Mouth", "Mikey"],
    correctAnswer: "Data",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the character who drives the ORV?",
    options: ["Brand", "Mikey", "Data", "Mouth"],
    correctAnswer: "Brand",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the character who is chained up in the basement?",
    options: ["Sloth", "Chunk", "Jake", "Francis"],
    correctAnswer: "Sloth",
  },
];

export default TheGooniesQuestions;
